<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Apache APISIX</title>
    <link>https://apisix.incubator.apache.org/zh/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Apache APISIX</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 11:46:04 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://apisix.incubator.apache.org/zh/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>两步验证</title>
      <link>https://apisix.incubator.apache.org/zh/contribute/2fa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 11:46:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://apisix.incubator.apache.org/zh/contribute/2fa/</guid>
      <description>Two-factor authentication(2FA) Two factor authentication (2FA) refers to the authentication method that combines both passport and an object (credit card, SMS phone, token or biomarkers as fingerprint) to identify a user. To ensure the security of the committer’s account, we need you to enable 2FA to sign in and contribute codes on GitHub. More details, please refer to 2FA.
Note:If you do not enable 2FA, you will be removed from the project and unable to access our repositories and the fork from our private repository.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>团队</title>
      <link>https://apisix.incubator.apache.org/zh/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 11:46:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://apisix.incubator.apache.org/zh/team/</guid>
      <description>成员 PPMC ID GitHub 账户 公开名称  yousa  Miss-you Hui Li  shuaijinchao  shuaijinchao JinChao Shuai  chenjunxu  nic-chen Junxu Chen  tangke  supermario1990 Ke Tang  totemofwolf  totemofwolf Lang Wang  lizhiyong  zhiyong0804 Li Zhiyong  liling  lilien1010 Ling Li  linsir  linsir Linsir Wu  wenming  moonming Ming Wen  wusheng  wu-sheng Sheng Wu  coolsoul  soulsoul Suo Zhang  agile6v  agile6v Wei Liu  liyong  chnliyong Yong Li  membphis  membphis YuanSheng Wang  juzhiyuan  juzhiyuan Zhiyuan  sshniro  sshniro Nirojan Selvanathan   提交者 下列名单不包含上方表格成员。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>提交者指南</title>
      <link>https://apisix.incubator.apache.org/zh/contribute/committer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 11:46:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://apisix.incubator.apache.org/zh/contribute/committer/</guid>
      <description>  加入提交者 Apache APISIX 社区遵照 Apache 社区 流程来接受新的提交者，当一位贡献者非常活跃时，PMC、PPMC 以及提交者将共同决定是否邀请该贡献者加入社区。
流程如下：
1. 在 @private 邮件列表中发起讨论，注意：当前只有 PMC 可以提名；
2. 如果投票通过，将发送邀请函以成为提交者，需 CC @private 邮件列表；
3. 新的提交者签署 ICLA 并提交有意愿的 Apache ID 与邮箱地址；
4. 更新 团队 页。
  职责 1. 开发新功能；
2. 重构代码；
3. 及时尽责地审阅 PR；
4. 讨论新的需求；
5. 回复提问；
6. 更新文档与示例；
7. 提升流程与相关工具；
8. 指导新的贡献者加入社区。
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>订阅指南</title>
      <link>https://apisix.incubator.apache.org/zh/contribute/subscribe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 11:46:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://apisix.incubator.apache.org/zh/contribute/subscribe/</guid>
      <description>  在使用 Apache APISIX 的过程中，若遇到任何问题，或有建议、想法，请大胆地使用 Appache 邮件列表与社区成员互动。
1. 发送邮件以订阅：使用你的常用邮箱，发送一封包含任意内容的邮件至 dev-subscribe@apisix.apache.org 。
2. 发送确认订阅邮件：第一步完成后，你将收到一封来自 dev-help@apisix.apache.org 的邮件，（若没有收到，请稍后检查诸如 RSS Feeds、垃圾邮件等选项卡）。接着，请回复任意内容至该邮件，以便完成订阅确认。
3. 接收欢迎邮件：完成上述步骤后，你将收到一封题为 WELCOME to dev@apisix.apache.org 的邮件，这表示你已成功订阅该邮件列表。
4. 此后，你将可以通过该邮箱收到 Apache APISIX 最新的邮件，也欢迎你通过邮件列表与社区交流！
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>贡献者指南</title>
      <link>https://apisix.incubator.apache.org/zh/contribute/contributor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 11:46:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://apisix.incubator.apache.org/zh/contribute/contributor/</guid>
      <description>Please fee free to report bugs, submit suggestions, or submit PRs according to this guide.
Submit an issue 1. Before submitting your issues, please go through a comprehensive search to make sure the problem cannot be solved just by searching.
2. Check the Issue List to make sure the problem is not repeated.
3. Create a new issue and choose the type of issue.
4. Define the issue with a clear and descriptive title.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>安全</title>
      <link>https://apisix.incubator.apache.org/zh/contribute/security/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 11:46:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://apisix.incubator.apache.org/zh/contribute/security/</guid>
      <description>The Apache Software Foundation takes a rigorous stance on eliminating security issues in its software projects. Apache Incubator APISIX is also very concerned Security issues related to its features and functionality.
If you have apprehensions regarding APISIX’s security or you discover vulnerability or potential threat, don’t hesitate to get in touch with the Apache Security Team by dropping a mail at security@apache.org. Please specify the project name as Incubator APISIX and its product name APISIX or APISIX-Dashboard in the email and provide a description of the relevant problem or potential threat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>发布指南</title>
      <link>https://apisix.incubator.apache.org/zh/contribute/release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 11:46:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://apisix.incubator.apache.org/zh/contribute/release/</guid>
      <description>GPG 设置 安装 GPG 在 GnuPG 官网下载安装包。 GnuPG 的 1.x 版本和 2.x 版本的命令有细微差别，下列说明以 GnuPG-2.1.23 版本为例。
安装完成后，执行以下命令查看版本号。
1 2  gpg --version    创建 Key 安装完成后，执行以下命令创建key。
GnuPG-2.x可使用：
1 2  gpg --full-gen-key    GnuPG-1.x可使用：
1 2  gpg --gen-key    根据提示完成key：
注意：请使用Apache mail生成GPG的Key。
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22 23 24 25 26 27 28 29 30 31 32 33 34  gpg (GnuPG) 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>下载</title>
      <link>https://apisix.incubator.apache.org/zh/downloads/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 23:48:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://apisix.incubator.apache.org/zh/downloads/</guid>
      <description>Releases Apache APISIX is released as source code tarballs. The downloads are distributed via mirror sites and should be checked for tampering using GPG or SHA-512. Version Release date Source download  0.9 2019 November 24 source ( asc sha512 )   1.0 2020 January 15 source ( asc sha512 )   1.1 2020 February 24 source ( asc sha512 )   1.2 2020 April 20 source ( asc sha512 )   1.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>